<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Allen Armstrong</title>
 <link href="http://words.allenarmstrong.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://words.allenarmstrong.com/"/>
 <updated>2015-02-09T00:37:46-05:00</updated>
 <id>http://words.allenarmstrong.com</id>
 <author>
   <name>Allen Armstrong</name>
   <email></email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Introduction</title>
   <link href="http://words.allenarmstrong.com/blog/introduction"/>
   <updated>2015-02-08T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://words.allenarmstrong.com/blog/introduction</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hello and welcome. I&amp;#39;ve decided to redesign my main site allenarmstrong.com into 2 identities &amp;mdash; &lt;a href=&quot;http://music.allenarmstrong.com&quot;&gt;My Music&lt;/a&gt; and this site, &lt;a href=&quot;http://words.allenarmstrong.com&quot;&gt;The Words I Write&lt;/a&gt;. The old site was a portfolio site to show off my work to clients or potenial new employers, but as I tell recruiters (almost everday)... I&amp;#39;m not looking for work right now. I&amp;#39;m very happy with where I&amp;#39;m at now. I&amp;#39;m a web desinger/developer for &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.flvs.net&quot;&gt;Florida Virtual School&lt;/a&gt; and I really am happy and love what I&amp;#39;m doing. I design the course-ware that educates the youth of Florida and wordwide. I&amp;#39;ve been designing and building websites since the mid 90&amp;#39;s, and most of them have been in one way or the other, trying to sell you something. Cars, Motorcycles, Vacations, Software, Video games, clothing, stocks... you name it, I&amp;#39;ve built a site trying to sell it. What I&amp;#39;m doing at FLVS is so rewarding, knowing it&amp;#39;s educating the youth. I get to work from home, I get paid well and the people are the greatest... whats not to love, why would I want a new job?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The previous site was a Wordpress site... and like so many others, I decided that it&amp;#39;s become a little more than what I really need. I&amp;#39;ve used it since 07 or 08 when I first started blogging. I had a photoblog - I Don&amp;#39;t Blame You - for awhile and many other little projects and sites running on WP. But now I just want something that would be easy to maintain, fast with little overhead... don&amp;#39;t have to worry about constantly applying security patches and updates. I&amp;#39;ve been reading about flat-file CMS&amp;#39;s for the last year or so, and even played around a little with some. I&amp;#39;ve finally decided to go in on Jekyll.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what is this site going to be about... basically a little about everything. I&amp;#39;ll probably still post about projects at work, or some of my photography... so it will still sorta be a portfolio... but in a different format. A personal portfolio.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But this just be a brain dump - link sharing blog. I didn&amp;#39;t want it to be. And I think that&amp;#39;s why I decided to go with a flat-file system as well.. thats one of the beauties of it. I think it will require more thought and purpose behind every post. To go through and format your post, the republish, commit the changes, ect. It&amp;#39;s more methodical, more to the process... and I like that. It&amp;#39;s almost like an art, each step important in the total outcome. Like back in the day, when I wrote more often for zines - it was a process and an art.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
